http://www.jannettesrareyarns.co.uk/privacy-policy.html

Translate Privacy Policy and Cookies  This privacy policy sets out how Jannette's Rare Yarns uses and protects any information that you give Jannette's Rare Yarns when you use this website.Jannette's Rare Yarns is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.Jannette's Rare Yarns may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 1st January 2013.What we collectWe may collect the following information: name and job title contact information including email address demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers What we do with the information we gatherWe require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons: Internal record keeping. We may use the information to improve our products and services. We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided. From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests. SecurityWe are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. We do not store credit card details nor do we share customer details with any third parties.How we use cookiesA cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website. Controlling your personal information You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways: whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at info@jannettesrareyarns.co.uk We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen. If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect. Shop ProductsYarnsPatterns & books Vintage yarn & books Knitting needles Crochet hooks Shade cards Knitting KitsAccessoriesSitemapCustomer ServicesDelivery & shipping How to shop Currency ConversionTerms & ConditionsLoyalty PointsPaymentPrivacy PolicyAbout UsContact us About usFollow me on TwitterFollow me on FacebookRelocation to Ireland© 2020 Jannette's Rare Yarns.  Contact us - About us - Delivery & shipping - How to shop 0               Total: $0.00 | View basket Sign in  -  New account  -  WishlistYarnBrands: A - FArtyarns in StockArtyarns to OrderFilatura di CrosaBrands: J-MJamieson of ShetlandLion BrandMondialBrands: N - ZRegiaRowanSock YarnWest Yorkshire SpinnersVintage Yarns & BooksVintage Christian de Falbe PatternsVintage Knitting BooksVintage Jaeger YarnVintage Rowan & Jaeger Patterns and BooksVintage Rowan YarnVintage Rowan Shade CardsPatterns & BooksDesigners: A - GAlice Starmore BooksAnnabel Fox Knitting PatternsArtyarns PatternsAssorted PatternsBrooklyn Tweed PatternsDesigners: I- MJaeger PatternsKim Hargreaves BooksDesigners: N - ZRowan Classic PatternsRowan MagazinesRowan Pattern BooksRowan Patterns - FreeRowan Studio CollectionWest Yorkshire Spinners PatternsAccessoriesAccessories A - HBag Handles & FormsBeads and CrystalsBucklesButtonsCatori Tablet / iPad CasesDebbie Bliss HomewareDog breeds luggage tagsGarment LabelsGift vouchersAccessories I-ZIron on appliquéKitsKnitting bags & needle casesPrym brass kilt pinsReady to wearRowan gift wrapShawl pinsStitch MarkersYarn KeepersLaurel Burch acessoriesLaurel Burch greeting cards & giftsLaurel Burch phone, tablet cases & luggage tagsLaurel Burch silk scarvesLaurel Burch socksSpecial offers A - BBargain Crochet HooksBargain pattern booksBargain Rowan & Jaeger buttonsBargain Rowan / Jaeger beadsBargain Rowan kilt pinsBargain Rowan opaque plastic buttonsBargain Rowan translucent buttonsC - LCheap and CheerfulFilatura di Crosa knitting yarn special offersLotus Special OffersN - ZRegia Sock YarnsRowan Angora Haze Special OfferRowan & Rowan classic knitting yarn special offersNoro Special OffersRowan Kidsilk Creation in Unreleased ShadesShade cardsNeedles & hooksKnitting NeedlesCrochet Hooks
